Guide to the Sumner McKnight Crosby Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Sumner McKnight Crosby papers
1937-1977
MS 1144
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
9
(23 boxes)
Correspondence, minutes of meetings, and reports documenting Crosby's Yale-related work, and his service on various commissions on the arts outside of Yale. The papers record his activities as chairman of the History of Art Department (1947-1953, 1962-1965), as advisor to the Audio-Visual Center, and as curator of Medieval Art at the Yale Art Gallery. His membership on commissions to preserve works of art damaged in World War II, and to foster international exchange programs in the arts is shown through the memoranda and publications of these groups. Among these groups are the American Commission for the Protection and Salvage of Artistic and Historic Monuments in War Areas, the American Council of Learned Societies, the American Federation of the Arts, the College Art Association, the United States Advisory Committee on the Arts, and the United States National Commission for UNESCO. There is very little material on his major scholarly contribution, namely the excavation of the Abbey of St. Denis. His correspondents include James S. Ackerman, Jean Bony, André Chastel, Henri Focillon, Theodore Sizer, Whitney Snow Stoddard and Denys Sutton.
Crosby, Sumner McK. (Sumner McKnight), 1909-1982
Conditions Governing Access
Material in boxes 19 and 20 is closed to researchers for 75 years, or as late as 2051. Restriction dates are indicated at the folder level.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred from the Yale University School of Art, 1977-1978.
Arrangement
Correspondence is arranged alphabetically.
Scope and Contents
The papers of Sumner McKnight Crosby range over the years 1937-1977, the duration of his work in the History of Art Department at the Yale University School of Art. The papers do not appear to be complete, but most of his activities are at least partially represented and documented. The bulk of the collection is papers from organizational committees on which Crosby served; these take the form of official minutes, related correspondence, and printed matter. Most of this material is not directly related to Yale, but is concerned either with the preservation of works of art damaged in World War II, or with international exchange programs in the arts. The papers which do show Crosby's work at the university are for the most part memos and correspondence from the History of Art Department, the Audio-Visual Center, and the Art Gallery, as well as Crosby's own correspondence with students. There is also a small amount of personal correspondence and other personal papers.
The collection presently fills 20 gray boxes and 1 large gray box. Three-quarters of it is arranged as correspondence; but personal papers (not correspondence), some printed matter, and restricted material have been kept separate. The restricted material falls into two categories: papers concerning Yale students and employees, and papers concerning other letters of recommendation.
Art; World War, 1939-1945; Art historians; Educators; Ackerman, James S., 1919-2016; Bony, Jean; Chastel, André, 1912-1990; Crosby, Sumner McK. (Sumner McKnight), 1909-1982; Focillon, Henri, 1881-1943; Sizer, Theodore, 1892-1967; Stoddard, Whitney S., 1913-; Sutton, Denys, 1917-; American Commission for the Protection and Salvage of Artistic and Historic Monuments in War Areas; American Council of Learned Societies; American Federation of Arts; College Art Association of America; Abbaye de Saint-Denis (Saint-Denis, France); U.S. National Commission for UNESCO; United States Advisory Commission on the Arts; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University. Art Gallery; Yale University. Department of the History of Art
- Inventory
  - Correspondence
    - Ackerman, James S., 1942 March 22 - 1952 June 4 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - American Association of Museums: Committee on Preparation for Museum Work, 1947 February 5 - 1948 June 15 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - American Commission for the Protection and Salvage of Artistic and Historic Monuments in War Areas, 1943 August - 1944 December 15, 1945 January 8 - May 10, 1945 May 14 - August 31, 1945 September 26 - 1955 January 26, undated (Box 1, Folder 3-7)
    - American Council of Learned Societies
      - General, 1941 February 4 - 1959 April 10, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Annual meetings, 1947, 1948-1950, undated (Box 2, Folder 9-11)
      - Committee on Research and Publication in the Fine Arts, 1941 June 13 - 1942 May 27, 1942 Junee 11 - 1943 January 26, undated (Box 2, Folder 12-13)
      - Conference Board of Associated Research Councils, 1947 May 14 - 1948 December 22 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Executive Committee, Board of Directors, 1947 January 11 - 1955 June 24 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Exploratory Committee on the Visual Arts, 1947 December 23 - 1949 January 15 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Publications, 1948-1960 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Secretaries of Constituent Societies, 1949 February 7 - 1950 January 31 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - American Federation of Arts
      - General, 1941 April 21 - 1945 December 19, 1949 August 8 - 1953 September 25, undated (Box 3, Folder 19-20)
      - Executive Committee, Board of Trustees, 1940 November 7 - 1942 November 18, 1943 February 17 - 1951 December 13, 1952 January 8 - 1958 December 9 (Box 3, Folder 21-23)
      - Magazine of Art, [1941 pre-October 25] - [1942 Aug(?)], 1942 September 2 - 1951 February 3, 1951 March 9 - 1953 March 31, undated (Box 3, Folder 24-26)
    - American Federation of Arts: minor publications, 1941-1951, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - American Institute of France, 1946 January 24, February 20 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - American Journal of Archaeology, 1948 January 19, January 21 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - American Philosophical Society, 1947 April 10 - 1950 February 21 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - American Society of Architectural Historians
      General note
      See: box 8, folder 94
    - American University Union, 1946 April 23 - 1948 May 27, 1949 January 4 - November 17 (Box 4, Folder 31-32)
    - Archaeological Institute of America, [1945 pre-November 6] - 1968 March 1 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Art in America, 1945 November 16, 1965 July 27 - 1966 June 3 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Art Quarterly, 1949 October 27, 1950 March 3 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Aubert, Marcel, 1941 July 8 - 1958 March 31. (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Aubert, Marcel: bank statements, 1946 October 31 - 1949 September 13 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Baltrusaitis, Jurgis and Hélène May, 1946 January 10 - [1949], 1950 January 27 - 1953 January 8, 1972 November 13, undated (Box 4, Folder 38-39)
    - Bliss, Robert Woods
      See: box 6, folder 67
    - Bobbs-Merrill Company, Inc.: Reprint Series in the History of Art, 1966 July 1 - 1967 December 16, 1968 January 12 - 1971 September 10, undated (Box 4, Folder 40-41)
    - Bollingen Foundation: Emile Mâle Project, 1966 January 21 - 1970 January 8 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Bony, Jean, 1948 April 16 - 1972 November 16 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching, 1939 January 24 - 1940 October 26 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Centre d' Études Supérieures de Civilisation Médiévale, 1964 February 15 - 1968 October 28 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Century Association, 1948 June 2 - 1969 October 7 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Chastel, André, 1948 November 11 - 1951 January 11 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Citizens for Eisenhower-Nixon, 1952 October 30 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - College Art Association
      - General, [post-1942 May] - 1972 November 10 (Box 5, Folder 49)
      - Art Bulletin, 1940 January 5 - 1964 January 21, undated (Box 5, Folder 50)
      - Executive Committee, Board of Directors, 1945 May 26 - 1948 December 3, 1949 January 29 - 1953 July 8 (Box 5, Folder 51-52)
      - Medieval Session, 1951 February 28 - 1952 February 8 (Box 5, Folder 53)
      - Minor publications, undated (Box 5, Folder 54)
      - National Committee for the History of Art, 1950 April 24 - 1963 January 18 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - College Art Association: Nominating Committee, 1951 January 19 - 1966 June 3 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Comité International d'Histoire de l'Art:
      - General, 1949 July 26 - 1964 July 1 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Congrès International, 1948 December 14 - 1958 April 30, 1948 May 3 - 1962 October 19 (Box 5, Folder 58-59)
      - Congrès International: publications, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Connecticut Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1948 December 19; 1968 September 23, October 7 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Cook, Walter William Spencer, 1947 August 21 - 1950 November 30 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Corpus Vitrearum Medii Aevi, 1954 February 11 - 1972 December 28 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Davidson, J. LeRoy, 1955 June 20 - 1959 January 29 (Box 6, Folder 63a)
    - Devinoy, Pierre, 1947 October 11 - 1969 May 12 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Focillon, Henri, and Marguerite, 1940 April 14 - 1957 November 27, undated (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Focillon, Henri, Society of the United States, 1940 January 3 - 1947 December 23, 1948 January 8 - 1972 September 29, undated (Box 6, Folder 66-67)
      See also: box 4, folder 36 box 4, folder 38 box 5, folder 43 box 5, folder 47 box 6, folder 70 box 6, folder 77
    - Foote School, New Haven, Connecticut, 1949 March 17 - 1965 May 18, undated (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Frick Collection, 1942 March 28 - 1963 March 25 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Grodecki, Louis, 1947 November 25 - 1966 February 23, undated (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Grolier Club, 1965 November 18, December 9 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Guggenheim, John Simon, Memorial Foundation, [1946 pre-November 6] - 1948 March 24 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Harvard University, 1950 March 9 - 1966 May 10 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - International Association of Art Critics, 1951 July (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - International Center of Medieval Art, 1956 March 1 - 1970 April 14 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - International Center of Romanesque Art
      See: box 6, folder 75
    - International Grenfell Association, 1952 July 29 - October 7 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Lavedan, Pierre, [1947 pre-September 26(?)] - October 28 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Levi-Strauss, Claude
      See: box 6, folders 66-67
    - Mediæval Academy of America, 1946 May 1 - 1967 August 14 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1964 April 7 - 1969 July 17 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - National Council of Churches: Department of Worship and the Arts, 1954 November 16 - 1957 July 30 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - National Cyclopedia of American Biography, 1965 January 28, April 6 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Oquossoc Angling Association, 1949 August 15 - 1959 June 15 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Phillips Academy, Andover, Massachusetts: general, [1943(?)] - 1965 March 3 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Phillips Academy, Andover, Massachusetts: Alumni Council, 1949 June 13 - 1953 March 18 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Phillips Academy, Andover, Massachusetts: Committee on the Addison Gallery, 1946 November 19 - [1952 May 3(?)] (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Princeton University: Advisory Council of the Department of Art and Archaeology, 1959 January 19 - 1966 May 27 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Revue de l' Art, undated (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1946 March 29, April 10 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Seymour, Charles, Jr.: papers concerning death of, 1977 April 9, [post-April 9] (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - Sizer, Theodore, 1947, 1960 April 20 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Société d'Histoire de France, 1949 March 10 - November 30 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Société Nationale des Antiquaires de France, 1946 July 3, 1964 February 7 - 1965 March-30 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Society for the History of Technology, 1967 December 28 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Society of Architectural Historians, 1945 November 7, 1957 November 21 - 1967 November 29 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Stoddard, Whitney Snow, 1947 November 12 - 1965 December 14 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - Sutton, Denys, 1945 September 24 - 1965 December 15 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - Textile Museum of the District of Columbia, 1945 December 13 - 1947 January 20 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - United States Advisory Committee on the Arts
      - Formation, first meeting (1958 Jan 15-16), 1957 January - 1958 January (Box 8, Folder 98-99)
      - Second meeting (1958 May 12-14), 1958 February-June (Box 8, Folder 100-101)
      - Third meeting (1958 Oct 6-7), 1958 July-October (Box 8, Folder 102-103)
      - Fourth meeting (1959 Feb 2), 1958 December - 1959 February (Box 9, Folder 104)
      - Fifth meeting (1959 May 18-19), 1959 March-May (Box 9, Folder 105)
      - Sixth meeting (1959 Oct 26-27), 1959 June-October (Box 9, Folder 106-107)
      - Seventh meeting (1960 Jan 18-19), 1959 November - 1960 January (Box 9, Folder 108)
      - Eighth meeting (1960 Apr 25-26), 1960 February-April (Box 9, Folder 109)
      - Ninth meeting (1960 Sep 12-13), 1960 May-September (Box 9, Folder 110-111)
      - Tenth meeting (1960 Oct 5), 1960 October-November (Box 9, Folder 112)
      - Eleventh meeting (1960 Dec 20-21), 1960 December (Box 10, Folder 113)
      - Twelfth meeting (1961 Feb 28-Mar 1), 1961 January - 1963 Feb, undated (Box 10, Folder 114)
      - American National Exhibition in Moscow (1959 Jul 25 - Sep 10(?), 1958 January - 1960 May (Box 10, Folder 115-116)
      - Expense Accounts, 1958 January - 1961 March (Box 11, Folder 117)
      - Foreign Service dispatches, 1958 August - 1961 March (Box 11, Folder 118-120)
      - Information Center Service: monthly progress reports, 1960 May - 1961 March (Box 12, Folder 121)
      - International Council at the Museum of Modern Art, 1959 July - 1960 May (Box 12, Folder 122)
      - Miscellaneous notes, 1959-1960, undated (Box 12, Folder 123)
      - National Council on the Arts and Government, 1959 January - 1961 December (Box 12, Folder 124)
      - Photographs, 1958 Jan, 1959 May (Box 12, Folder 125)
    - United States National Commission for UNESCO, [1947 post-February 15] - 1954 February 15 (Box 12, Folder 126)
    - United-States National Commission for UNESCO, 1954 March 23 - [March(?)], [1954 March(?)] - April 9 (Box 12, Folder 127-129)
    - United States National Commission for UNESCO, 1954 April 15-29 (Box 12, Folder 130)
    - United States National Commission for UNESCO, 1954 May 2-11, 1954 May 13 - August 25, 1954 August 30 - 1965 November 3 (Box 13, Folder 131-133)
    - United States Office of Education: Wartime Commission: Committee on Art, 1942 May 26 - 1943 July 7 (Box 13, Folder 134)
    - United States Office of War Information, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 134a)
    - United States Senate: Committee on Foreign Relations, 1960 September 29 - 1961 March 28 (Box 13, Folder 135)
    - University of North Carolina, 1953 June 1 - 1965 June 4 (Box 13, Folder 136)
    - University of Texas, 1968 March 18, 26 (Box 13, Folder 137)
    - Ventures, 1965 July 9 - December 13 (Box 13, Folder 138)
    - Verdier, Philippe, 1954 September 24 - 1967 January 13 (Box 13, Folder 138a)
    - Vermont Academy, 1963 September 26, October 3 (Box 13, Folder 139)
    - Yale Club of New York, 1958 April 28 - 1967 March 23 (Box 13, Folder 140)
    - Yale College: general, 1941 November 13 - 1956 September 15, undated (Box 13, Folder 141)
    - Yale College: Committee on the Course of Study, 1945 January 20 - [1956 post-April 26] (Box 13, Folder 142)
    - Yale College: Directed Studies, 1946-1954, undated (Box 13, Folder 143)
    - Yale College: Directed Studies: History of Art I, 1952 August 21 - 1955 October 4, undated (Box 13, Folder 144)
    - Yale Mediæval Non-Club, Conjurated, [1954 pre-March 15(?)] - 1963 October 22, undated (Box 14, Folder 145)
    - Yale University: general, 1941 December 30 - 1967 December 28, undated (Box 14, Folder 146)
    - Yale University Alumni Board, 1952 February 6 - 1956 May 24 (Box 14, Folder 147)
    - Yale University Alumni Board: Film Committee, 1952 November 13 - 1955 November 9, 1955 December 2 - 1957 December 6, undated (Box 14, Folder 148-149)
    - Yale University Art Gallery, 1947 February 14 - 1974 February 14, undated (Box 14, Folder 150)
    - Yale University Audio-Visual Center: general, 1951 November 6 - [1953(?)], 1954 May 19 - 1957 March 4, undated (Box 14, Folder 151-152)
    - Yale University Audio-Visual Center: Film Series, 1955 September 29 - [1956 pre-September 15(?)] (Box 14, Folder 153)
    - Yale University Audio-Visual Center: report, 1956 September (Box 14, Folder 154)
    - Yale University Audio-Visual Center: Television Project, 1951 June 13 - 1952 November 17, undated (Box 15, Folder 155)
    - Yale University
      - Berkeley College, 1945 November 19 - 1966 June 6, undated (Box 15, Folder 156)
      - Berkeley Portraits, 1946 December 13 - 1947 November 18, 1969 May 13 (Box 15, Folder 157)
      - Division of the Arts, [1948 post-February 3] - 1955 October 15 (Box 15, Folder 158)
      - Division of the Arts: Committee on Slides and Photographs, 1948 July 22 - 1956 October 16 (Box 15, Folder 159)
      - Foreign Area Studies, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 159a)
      - Graduate School, 1947 September 1 - 1972 December 11 (Box 15, Folder 160)
      - History of Art Department
        Original folder reads: History of Art Plan
        [ Not to go to Woodbridge Hall for filing. Keep here temporarily; to be destroyed after a while per CS, Jan 1940 and Jul 1940]
        - General, 1940 May 25 - 1949 July 1, [1951] - 1971 March 12, undated (Box 15, Folder 161-162)
        - Budgets, 1947 September 24 - 1955 October 21 (Box 15, Folder 163)
        - Course enrollments, 1947 February 6 - 1966 April 27 (Box 15, Folder 164)
        - Curriculum, course materials, 1941 December 22 - [1967], undated (Box 15, Folder 165)
        - Faculty appointments, 1947 Spring - 1955 November 1 (Box 15, Folder 166)
        - History of Art Series, 1947 December 30 - 1969 October 29 (Box 15, Folder 167)
        - Organization, 1939 October 11 - 1940 January 17 (Box 15, Folder 168)
          Scope and Contents
          Original folder reads: History of Art Plan [Not to go to Woodbridge Hall for filing. Keep here temporarily; to be destroyed after a while per CS, Jan 1940 and Jul 1940]
        - Teaching Films Project, 1949 May 25 - 1955 October 31, undated (Box 15, Folder 169)
        - Visiting lecturers (Box 15, Folder 170)
          See also: box 6, folders 66-67
        - Visual Approach to History, 1948 June - 1950 June 30 (Box 15, Folder 171)
    - Yale University Library, 1947 June - [1948(?)], 1949 January 19 - 1968 April 10, undated (Box 15, Folder 172-173)
    - Yale University: Wolf's Head Society, 1946 November 21 - 1963 October 31 (Box 16, Folder 174)
    - Correspondence with publishers, 1949 October 24 - 1975 November 5 (Box 16, Folder 175)
    - Correspondence re: Saint-Denis, 1947 October 22 - 1974 April 15 (Box 16, Folder 176)
    - Lecture invitations, 1946 [Mar(?)] - 1965 February 24 (Box 16, Folder 177)
    - Correspondence re: personal art collection, 1946 April 11 - 1965 May 26 (Box 16, Folder 178)
    - Correspondence re: awards and honorary degrees, 1950 March 7 - 1965 June 4 (Box 16, Folder 179)
    - Correspondence re: fishing, 1950 October 2, 1956 February 29, 1968 January 2 (Box 16, Folder 180)
    - Miscellaneous and unidentified, [1924(?)], 1947 May 14 - 1969 November 1, undated (Box 16, Folder 181)
  - Personal Papers
    - Notices of appointments, promotions, leaves of absence, 1946 February 9 - 1971 January 30 (Box 16, Folder 182)
    - Book reviews, abstracts, [1945(?)] - 1950 August 15 (Box 16, Folder 183)
    - Personal bibliography, 1947 March 20 - 1953 Jan, undated (Box 16, Folder 184)
    - Clippings, [1946 Mar(?)] - 1952 June 11 (Box 16, Folder 185)
    - Photographs, 1651 May, undated (Box 16, Folder 186)
  - Printed Matter
    - Regarding preservation of war-damaged works of art, 1944-1954, 1961 (Box 21B, Folder 1-8, Box 21A, Folder 1-4, Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Regarding international cultural exchange programs
      - President's Special International Program: semi-annual reports, 1956-1960 (Box 17, Folder 187-188)
      - Institute of International Education: News Bulletin, 1957 December - 1961 April (Box 17, Folder 189)
      - Educational and Cultural Exchange Program: semi-annual reports to Congress, 1958-1960 (Box 17, Folder 190)
      - Miscellaneous, 1940-1956 Oct, 1957 July - 1960 Mar, 1960 June 3 - 1961 April 1 (Box 18, Folder 191-193)
      - Brochures of international exchange exhibitions, 1956-1958 (Box 18, Folder 194)
  - Restricted Material
    - Yale College
      - Committee on the Marshall-Allison Fellowship, 1946 May 17 - 1948 February 20, 1948 March 2 - 1969 November 7, undated (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
        Conditions Governing Access
        Materials in folders 1-2 are restricted until January 1, 2045 due to University policy set by the Yale Corporation.
      - Correspondence with undergraduates (past, present, prospective), 1941 - 1974 January 2, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
        Materials in folder 3 are restricted until January 1, 2050 due to University policy set by the Yale Corporation.
      - Undergraduate grade books, [1941(?)]-1972 (Box 19, Folder 4-5)
        Materials in folders 4-5 are restricted until January 1, 2048 due to University policy set by the Yale Corporation.
    - Yale University Audio-Visual Center: recommendations re: employment, 1955 August 18 - 1957 May 1 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      Materials in folder 6 are restricted until January 1, 2033 due to University policy set by the Yale Corporation.
    - Yale University
      - History of Art Department: correspondence with graduate students (past, present, prospective), 1939 October 24 - [1946(?)] (Box 20, Folder 7)
        Materials in folder 7 are restricted until January 1, 2022 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
      - History of Art Department: correspondence with graduate students (past, present, prospective), 1947 January 22 - [1947] (Box 20, Folder 8)
        Materials in folder 8 are restricted until January 1, 2023 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
      - History of Art Department: correspondence with graduate students (past, present, prospective), 1948 January 10 - November 24 (Box 20, Folder 9)
        Materials in folder 9 are restricted until January 1, 2024 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
      - History of Art Department: correspondence with graduate students (past, present, prospective), 1948 December 14 - 1962 November 21 (Box 20, Folder 10)
        Materials in folder 10 are restricted until January 1, 2038 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
      - History of Art Department: correspondence with graduate students (past, present, prospective), 1963 February 12 - 1972 November 27 (Box 20, Folder 11)
        Materials in folder 11 are restricted until January 1, 2048 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
      - History of Art Department: correspondence with graduate students (past, present, prospective), 1973 June 20 - 1976 September 21, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
        Materials in folders 12 are restricted until January 1, 2052 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
      - History of Art Department: graduate scholarships and fellowships, 1941 March 4 - 1962 January-19, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
        Materials in folder 13 are restricted until January 1, 2038 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
      - Correspondence re: letters of recommendation (other than for students), 1943 June 27 - 1971 May 7, undated (Box 20, Folder 14)